原创翻译  双语字幕
最新连载海外影视剧下载
请登陆 www.YYeTs.com
仅供交流学习  禁止商用盈利
翻译     白夜君  草草  苏葵  小酸奶
校对     小酸奶
时间轴     紫夏  啾啾啾
后期     吉吉
总监     小酸奶
深入黑暗  第一季 第六集
莱利
你为什么要...
Why-- you have to--
你为什么要那么做
why are you doing it like that?
你得把它们叠好
You have to fold, fold, okay?
我们的时间可不多  拜托
We have very little time, left. Please.
我去  各位啊
Holy shit, you guys!
他在煮东西  是水
He's cooking something, it's water,
但恭喜了
but congratulations.
至少还在加热
There's heat involved.
是烹饪
It's cooking!
该死
Fuck!
谁赢了玉米粥挑战
Who won the polenta challenge?
我们待会儿再拍那个
We shoot that later, okay?
但如果要我说了算
But if it is up to me,
他们都赢不了  因为他们...
none of those people, because they're just--
他们全都太不会烹饪了
they're all so awful at cooking in general.
请别从我的吧台上掉下来
Please, please don't fall off my bar.
好吧  我就随便说说
Okay, look, I'm just spitballing here.
嗯  说吧
Mm-hm, sock it to me.
我想听
I want it.
你做我的伴
You be my plus one.
你要我去参加你妈的婚礼
You want me to crash your mom's wedding?
过来
Come here, come here.
但那会很奇怪的
But it's gonna be so weird.
坐下
Sit down.
小老鼠  我没受邀  好吗
Mouse, I wasn't invited, okay?
前任一般不会被请去
Ex-spouses don't usually make the cut.
收到
Copy that.
五分钟  雷克先生
Hey, five minutes, Mr. Rake.
好
Okay.
莱利
Riley, uh...
你妈妈非常爱你
your mom loves you very much.
我也非常爱你
And I love you very, very much,
虽然这不是竞争
not that it's a competition.
但听我说
But listen to me.
这周末之后
Nothing's gonna change
也不会有什么改变
after this weekend.
好吗
Okay?
但你妈妈的新姓氏将变成"盖可"
Except your mom's new last name will be "Geck."
这太不幸了
That's unfortunate.
我觉得我们该让他们好好度过这一天
So, I think we should just give them this day
然后下周末
and then next weekend,
我们俩
you and me?
我们去应付全世界
We take on the world.
好吗
Okay?
我们今晚就开始吧
Well, how about we start tonight?
达奈尔公园刚建成了新迷你高尔夫球场
Darnell Park just cut the ribbon on a new mini golf course.
所以我才叫凯蒂
And why do you think I gave Katie instructions
晚6点前送你过去
to have you there by 6 PM
这样你就可以站在
so that you can see the sun setting
新粉刷的1:1风车后面欣赏落日了
behind the freshly painted, sized-to-scale windmill?
好啊  伙计
Hey buddy.
拜托  这周末不行啊
Come on, not this weekend, man.
好吧  等一下的
Okay. Hey, one sec.
好吧
Oh! Okay.
我想陪你一起去打高尔夫吗
Look, do I want to be the one that golfs with you?
当然了  但我这周末有太多
Of course. I just have so much work to do
工作要做了  你应该得到
this weekend, and you deserve better
比我更专心的陪伴  好吗
than my distracted company, okay?
你陪我的时候往往是心不在焉
Yeah, well, your company's often distracted.
这个我承认
I handed that one to you, okay?
免费承认
I gave that to you for free.
系个蝴蝶结吧
Had a bow on it.
下周六
Next Saturday,
你  我  达奈尔公园
you, me, Darnell Park.
但我下周六要踢足球
Okay, but I have a soccer game next Saturday.
那是测试
It was a test.
恭喜  你通过了
Congratulations, you've passed.
我是想说  下周日
What I meant to say is next Sunday
我们肯定玩疯
will be off the chain.
别说"玩疯"
Never say "off the chain."
-反正是句俏皮话  -别傻了
- Whatever's clever. - Don't.
我都不知道现在流行语是什么了
I don't know what plays anymore.
亲爱的  什么流行
Babe, what plays?
告诉我
Tell me.
"酷"又回来了
Okay, well, "rad"'s back.
凯蒂  "酷"又回来了
Oh! Katie, "rad"'s back.
-你知道吗  -"酷"又回来了
- Did you know that? - "rad"'s back!
是啊  你好酷啊
Yeah. You are so rad.
你的乱发又很酷
Yeah, well, your floppy hair is rad.
开车要小心
Hey, um, please drive carefully
这可是我最贵重的货物
because this is my most precious cargo,
如果有什么情况打给我
and, uh, call me if anything goes sideways,
给自己弄点吃的
and would you please feed yourselves?
谢谢  周末愉快
Thanks. Have a great weekend.
-我们可以的  -当然
- We got this. - Of course.
嗯
Yup.
你是我的唯一
You are my only.
我需要你
I need you.
再见
Bye!
好吧
Okay.
巴里  我已经照你的要求做了
Barry, I have done what you've asked,
我周末要离镇
and I am skipping town for the weekend, okay?
拜托告诉我你要做什么
Now please tell me what you're doing,
剧透  最好是有牙的家伙
and, spoiler alert, it better have some fuckin' teeth.
树屋
巴里·斯特恩布什先生
你有火吗
You got a light?
嗯
Yeah.
给你了
Keep it.
我想戒呢
Trying to quit.
我们都想戒
We're all trying to quit.
我会对它视如己出
I'll treat her like she was my own.
-抱歉  -没事
- Ooh, sorry. - It's okay.
谢谢
Thank you.
好吧
All right.
好了  我们走吧
Ready, let's go.
好了  走吧
Okay, let's go.
这不够
It's not enough.
-行的  -什么
- No, it's good. - What?
这是什么啤酒
Wait, what kind of beer is that?
谁拿一下
Hold this, someone.
我理解你  但你不希望她们觉得
I am with you, but also you don't want them
你是拿女人皮做衣服的变态吧
to think you make suits out of lady skins, right?
我们走吧
Yes, let's go.
不会吧
No way.
彼得·雷克
Peter Rake.
是啊  我是彼得大厨本人
Yeah, yes, I am, I am Chef Peter in the flesh.
我去
Oh, holy shit.
你高中时就在这里工作  是吧
Holy shit, you used to work here in high school, didn't you?
莱尼
Lenny.
朗尼
Lonnie.
这里
This is, um...
现在是我的了
It's all mine now.
厉害  哥们
Booya, man, this is...
这真不错呢
this is really great for you.
嗯  我爸几年前死了
Yeah, my dad kicked the bucket a few years back.
被癌症吞噬了
The cancer ate him up.
我去  我很遗憾
Shit, I'm sorry to hear that, man.
没事的
It's okay.
他是个混蛋
He was a mean son of a bitch.
我老爸也是这样
Well, you know, the same thing happened to my old man,
他也不怎么样
and he wasn't much of a prize either.
嗯
Yeah.
现在只有我和我母亲了
So now it's just me and Mother.
"母亲"啊
"Mother," Huh?
你们考虑过多元化一下吗
You guys think about diversifying a little bit?
或许加几个房间
Maybe you could add a few rooms,
在墙上开个洞
poke some tiny holes in the wall,
改名叫贝茨旅馆
call it Bait Motel, huh?
朗尼  这里是什么
Lonnie, what's--what's down here?
你放篮子和换洗衣物的地方吗
Is this where you keep the baskets and the washing, huh?
抱歉  我太傻了
Sorry, that was stupid. It's--
这地方看上去很棒  真的
The place looks great, it really does.
你有垃圾桶
You know, you have bins,
全是鱼饵的挂画
stills just filled with bait.
真是一点没变
It's exactly the same.
太棒了
It's--it's great.
你妹妹以前常来
Yeah, sister used to come around
有一阵很频繁
pretty regular for a while.
我妹妹  对啊
Oh, my sister, that's right.
这样吧  我要一包库兹烟
Tell you what, I'll take a pack of Kools
不用找了
and--and keep the change.
-我请你了  -不  那怎么行
- It's on me. - No, that's ridiculous.
你的钱在这里没用
Your money's no good here.
这...
These...
很棒  你太贴心了
These are perfect, and that's-- that's sweet.
谢谢
Thank you, sir.
我会告诉格温...
I'm gonna tell Gwen that, uh--
等等
Wait, um...
她来了吗
Is she here?
没有
No, no, she's not.
她现在几乎不怎么来这边了
She--she hardly ever makes it down here.
她都不回来了
She never-- she never makes it back.
但我会告诉她...
But I'm gonna tell her that--
朗尼会说
Lonnie says...
*嗨  格温*
*Hey Gwennie*
她肯定会喜欢的
Yeah, she's gonna love that.
谢谢了
Thanks, man.
詹
Hey Zan.
洁雅
Hey Jayna.
我们那时真是神奇双胞胎
Oh, we are so Wonder Twinning right there.
说到青春时期
Speaking of our youth, uh...
艾格尼丝在我们小时候就60多了吧
Agnes was what, 60 years old when we were kids,
那她现在就...
which would put her at, right now,
至少一百了吧
at least a solid hunge, right?
-超过一百了  -嗯
- A hunge and a deuce? - Yeah.
那她也还能收拾你
And she would still whoop your ass.
他去楼上住
He'll be upstairs,
你父亲的旧办公室
your father's old office.
现在是卧室了
It's a bedroom now.
谢天谢地
Thank God.
我宁可睡外面
I would rather sleep outside
也不想睡我们死去父母冰冷的床
than in our dead parents' stone cold bed.
艾格尼丝  别这样
Hey, Agnes, please, please, please.
你不用替我把包拿到楼上
You don't have to carry my--my bag up the stairs.
我安排你去北欧水疗
Can I just--can I get you a weekend at a Nordic spa
玩一周末吧
or something?
不用了
No.
好吧
Okay.
我唯一的侄女怎么样了
So how's my one and only niece?
看看吧
Here you go.
天呐
Oh my God.
-开玩笑吗  -没有
- Are you kidding me? - I'm not kidding you.
她11岁了  越来越像米歇尔·奥巴马
She is 11 going on Michelle Obama.
我在图片分享上粉了她
Oh, I follow her on Instagram,
但她不怎么拍自拍
but she doesn't really do selfies.
我怎么也想不通
I've racked my brains, I can't figure out
她这谦虚的劲头跟谁学的
where she gets the humility from.
格温  我不知道
Gwen, I don't know.
-不是跟我学的  -是啊
- Not me. - No, not you.
没了吗
So that's it?
真的
Really?
就几份食谱
Just a couple recipes
和呼吸新鲜空气
and a few breaths of fresh air?
你就是为了这个而来吗
That's all that's going on here?
你不知道一直见不到你
I mean, you have no idea how fucked up it's been
没有你的消息  我都难受
not seeing you and not hearing from you.
我非常清楚这多难受
I'd argue I know exactly how fucked up it's been.
我的号码没变过
My number hasn't changed.
知道吗
You know?
我才是离了婚的那个
I'm the one who went through a divorce, right?
我才是不能参加爸爸葬礼的那个
I'm the one that wasn't welcome at Dad's funeral.
好  我知道了
Yeah, okay, point taken.
好
Okay.
你记得你上次对我
You remember what you said to me
说了什么吗
the last time?
我当时很艰难  格温  好吗
I was going through some shit, Gwen, okay?
然后爸爸剥夺了我的继承权
And then Dad cuts me out,
但我需要你
but I needed you to fuckin' have--
无论如何都支持你
Have your back no matter what.
是啊
Yeah.
你还好吗
Yeah, how have you been?
How have you been, you know?
你还在为正义而战吗
You're just still fightin' the good fight?
有跟谁约会吗
Datin' anybody?
因为我那么有闲吗
With all the free time I have?
该死
Ah, shit.
猜猜还有谁是单身
Guess who else is single?
-柯林·法瑞尔  -差远了
- Colin Farrell? - Not even close.
高中的朗尼
Lonnie from high school.
煮兔子的朗尼
Bunny boiler Lonnie.
嗯
Yeah.
他现在在自己开一家
He's running the bait shop
鱼饵店
all by himself now.
是啊
I know.
我已经很久没想过他了
I have not thought about him in a very long time.
天呐  如果你想他了我才担心呢
Well, I mean, Christ, I would be worried if you had.
但他说
But he does-- he does say...
*嗨  格温*
*Hey Gwennie*
你还有这个选择呢
So you've got that going for you.
-好吗  -你跟他说话了
- Okay? - You spoke to him?
是啊  他还有那个可爱的屁股下巴
I did, and he still has that sweet butt chin.
-好了  够了  -挺好的
- Okay, stop that. - It's nice, okay.
他只是想做我的朋友  你知道的
He was just trying to be my friend, you know that.
但你是军乐队的大号手
But you played the tuba in marching band.
格温  如果你还跟朗尼玩
Gwen, hanging out with Lonnie
你在高中就算
would have been the final death nail
别想翻身了
in your high school shit coffin.
不客气
You're welcome.
为什么现在见面
So why now?
我想你了
You know, I miss you.
你是我特别大脑的另一半
You're the other half of my very special brain.
得了
Come on.
我在这儿呢
I'm right here.
跟我说吧
Just talk to me.
是该死的互联网
It's the fuckin' internet.
你不能...
You can't...
我太容易针对了
I'm an easy target.
格温  你清楚的
Gwen, you know this, you know this.
我们已经尽可能地审查这些人了
We vet these people the best way we can,
但天呐  肯定要有人遭殃的
but, oh, God, heads are gonna roll.
相信我  敢惹公牛
Mark my words, you mess with the bull...
就被捅
You get the horns.
-知道了  -不  你不懂
- Got it. - No, you don't got it.
所以我们才三年没说话了
That's why we haven't spoken for three years, Gwen.
该死
Shit.
我得接一下
I gotta take this.
好吧
Oh, okay.
安迪  什么情况
Andy, what have you got?
你饿了吗
You hungry?
我们成农民了吗  艾格尼丝
Are we farmers, Agnes?
你说什么呢
What are you going on about?
那只魔鬼般的黑羊
I'm talking about Black Phillip
就在...
prancing about the...
好吧
Okay, well...
当我没说
never mind, but...
见到你很高兴  孩子
Good to see you, boy.
艾格尼丝
Agnes.
天呐  你真不会说谎
God, you are such a bad liar.
你会恨我的
You're gonna hate me.
"恨"是个强烈  不好摆脱的词
"Hate" is a strong and sticky word.
我得走了
I have to leave.
嗯  我双尸案的负责警探
Yeah. The, um, lead detective in my double homicide
刚抓了第二位枪手
just picked up the second shooter.
他们说他愿意开口
They're saying he's willing to talk,
但只肯对地检官说
but only to the DA,
而那是我
which happens to be me.
你吗
You?
难以置信
That's incredible.
那太难以置信了
That's fucking-- that's incredible.
什么时候
When, when?
-五个月了  -天呐
- Five months. - Oh my...
我想打给你的
Yeah, I wanted to call you, but--
我妹妹是地检官了
Shit, my sister is the DA.
你没开玩笑吧
You're not fucking kidding me?
我们得庆祝一下
We have to celebrate.
-我们庆祝吧  -我们会的
- Let's celebrate. - No, we will.
真的  我保证
We will, I promise, I promise.
我想陪你一周末的
Yeah, I wanted to spend the whole weekend with you.
没事
Okay, well, there's-- you know,
还有好多周末呢
there's endless weekends.
-是吗  -如果我说了算的话
- Really? - If I have my way, yes.
好
Okay.
我有新情况会告诉你
Well, I will call with updates.
那好
Please do.
-再见  -嗯
- Okay, bye. - Oh, yeah.
-谢谢  -好
- Thanks. - All right.
艾格尼丝  这墙上之前挂的
Hey, Ags, whatever happened
鲍勃·罗斯先生画的温婉的
to the gentle, Bob Ross-esque Alaskan landscape
阿拉斯加景色呢
that used to adorn this wall?
你父亲取下来了
Your father moved it
因为他开始画画了
when he took up painting.
他最后就干这个
It's pretty much all he did towards the end.
那是他画的
That one's his.
好啊
Nice.
但这什么玩意啊
But also, what the actual fuck?
他画的都是
His pieces were all about
生命的脆弱
the fragility of life.
他的葬礼如何
How was his funeral?
冰冷
Cold.
合适
That's fitting.
艾格尼丝
Uh, hey, Ags?
无意冒犯  但你考虑过
I don't mean any offense, but have you ever thought about
找医生看看
having a doctor take a look
你的眼睛吗
at those... sweet peepers?
何必
What for?
是我忘不了的事情
It's the things I can't unsee
让我夜不能寐
that keep me up at night.
艾格尼丝  可以接下电话吗
Ags, could you get the phone, please?
该死
Shit!
去你的
Oh, fuck you, man.
该死
Shit.
-喂  -彼得
- Hello? - Hi Peter.
我是朗尼
It's Lonnie.
鱼饵和鱼线的
From Bait and Tackle.
我知道你是谁  朗尼
I know who you are, Lonnie.
但我不知道黄页上有我们的电话
Um, didn't know this number was listed, though.
之前也是你打来的吗
Was that-- was that you that was calling earlier?
-哥们  -之前
- Buddy? - Earlier?
没有  不是我
Mm, no that wasn't me.
你确定你之前没打给我吗  朗尼
You--you sure you weren't calling me before, Lonnie?
我只是想确认你还好
I just wanted to make sure you're okay.
我挺好
Yeah, no, I'm okay.
谢谢  哥们
Thank you, man, I'm just--
我就小住一下
it's quick in, out, you know?
就拿几样东西
Pickin' up a few things, so...
朗尼  你还在吗
Lonnie, you still there?
你混得真不错  彼得
You did really good, Peter.
还上了电视什么的
On TV and everything.
我很为你高兴
I'm just really happy for you.
好吧
Okay.
该死
Shit.
彼得  我是巴里
Yo, Pete, it's Barry.
听我说  我调查过后
Uh... look dude, after doing some more recon,
相信我们能解决这个问题
I'm confident we'll be able to settle this, okay?
基本上就是重复取证
It's basically rinse and repeat.
这次没必要搞得太难看
There's no reason to drag this one through the mud
除非你想被记录在案
unless you're willing to go on record,
我当然不建议你这么做
which I certainly wouldn't advise.
你可以给我回电话
Uh, you can holler back
语音信箱
巴里·斯特恩布什先生
如果你想按照我的周末收费标准给钱的话
if you want me to bill you my weekend rate. Uh...
兄弟  放松一下
Look, dude, just try to relax.
别去网上探索未知世界  好吗
Don't go down any rabbit holes on the web, all right?
再见
Ciao.
你好  有什么事吗
Hi, can I help you?
你好
Hi.
我是不是在鱼饵和鱼线见过你
Didn't I see you back at the Bait and Tackle?
是的  我看见你了
Yes, yes, and I saw you.
有那么一瞬间
There--there was a-- there was a moment.
虽然很短暂  但我们四目相对了
It was brief, but we shared it.
你好  我是彼得
Hi, I'm Peter.
卡拉
Kara.
很抱歉打扰你
I'm-- I'm really sorry to bother you.
只是我们遇到了麻烦
We're just--we're in a pickle.
穿过峡谷之后车坏了
Cross the canyon lost power,
备用修理员珍妮筋疲力尽
back-up Jenny pooped out.
这就像是给单身女子的周末
It's putting a-- a big damper
装了个巨大的阻尼器
on bachelorette weekend.
-这真是...  -所以你需要手电筒
- So it's-- - You need flashlights,
蜡烛和午餐肉
candles, and SPAM.
-你读懂了我的心  -好吧  进来吧
- You read my mind. - Okay, come on in.
我们看看都有什么
Let's uh, see what we've got.
或者你就站在这儿
Or you stay right there
我把东西拿给你
and I will bring the items to you.
你不知道我是不是泰德·邦迪[连环杀手]  对吧
You don't know if I'm Ted Bundy, do you?
但我必须要警告你
Uh, but I have to warn you,
可能我需要花一分钟的时间
it might take me, like, a minute
去找我们刚刚说的物品
to find the items we're discussing
因为我自从锈根乐队解散之后
because I have not been home
就没来过这里
since Rusted Root was the shit.
你知道吗  彼得  很冷
You know what, Peter, it's-- it's cold.
我很冷  都怪我自己
I'm cold, and that's on me.
所以  带路吧
So lead the way.
好的
Okay.
我们可以把门开着
Uh, we can leave this door open.
你确实有他的颧骨
You know, you do have his cheekbones.
谁的颧骨
Whose cheekbones?
泰德·邦迪[连环杀手]
Ted Bundy.
你眼神真好
You are sharp.
只需要一点火花
It only takes a spark
但我们需要更多
but we need more.
这不是壁橱
That's not a closet.
确实不是
It's not.
很高兴知道
Good to know.
很高兴知道这不是
It's good to know.
我迷路了
I'm flying blind here.
我很抱歉
I'm so sorry.
没事的
That's all right.
这个地方真是...
This place is--
又脏又俗吗
Awful, tacky?
这点钱全都花错地方了
Everything that's wrong with old money?
品味是买不来的
There's just no accounting for taste.
你知道吗
You know what?
我本来想说"漂亮"的
I was gonna say "Beautiful."
这里的景色太美了
I mean, the views are incredible.
好吧
Okay.
所以你是一位音乐家  对吧
So, uh, you are a musician, huh?
我会读心啊
I read minds.
而且我注意到了你指尖上的老茧
Plus, I noticed the calluses on your fingertips,
这是这位女士弹吉他
which is a sure sign
确切的迹象
the young lady plays the six strings.
没错  我在咖啡店和二手书店
Yeah, I make the big bucks
弹琴赚了不少钱
playing coffee shops and used book stores, so...
吃了许多拉面
eat a lot of ramen.
我很欣赏这点
I can appreciate that.
就像你会很感谢这些一样
Just like you can appreciate these.
-彼得  -怎么了
- Peter? - Yes?
很多女士肯定会
I know a handful of ladies
认为你是真正的王子
who are gonna think you're a real prince.
那挺好
Ribbit.
如果事情变得更糟了  你有我的电话
Uh, you have my number if things deteriorate in a meaningful way.
我会的  邻居
I do, neighbor.
或者
Or, you know,
或许我只是牛奶喝完了
maybe I'll just run out of milk.
早上好  你这个老东西
Good morning, you old bastard.
讨厌的人得不到休息  是吧
No rest for the weary, huh?
我正处于盛年  混蛋
I'm in my prime, asshole.
拜托  拜托  不要
Please, please. No, no.
等等
Wait.
彼得
Peter!
-你好  -糟糕  抱歉
- Hey. - Oh, shit, I'm sorry.
我没看见你戴着耳机
I didn't-- I didn't see the ear buds.
-现在一切都说得通了  -是啊
- Everything makes sense now. - Yeah.
我当然没聋
No, I'm totally not deaf.
欢迎来到夏尔郡
Uh, welcome to The Shire.
是啊
Oh, yeah.
-树屋挺酷  -谢谢你
- Cool tree house. - Thank you.
非常感谢你
Thank you very much.
老天  真不敢相信它还没塌
Man, can't believe that thing is still standing.
以前我和我姐姐一到夏天就搬进去
Me and my sister used to basically move in there every summer.
现在有些混蛋在上面放了些奇怪的东西
Now, some jerk has put a weird thing on the thing,
你们最后怎么样了
but, hey, how did you guys make out?
你们的进展怎么样
How did you fare?
不是很好
Oh, not great.
电工要到星期一才能上班
The electrician can't get out till Monday.
-但是...  -糟糕
- But... - Shit.
世事无常  要勇敢面对
Lemonade out of lemons.
昨天晚上还是很愉快的
Last night ended up being really fun.
-挺好的  -是的
- Oh, nice. - Yeah.
-你好  乌龟  -这不是比赛
- Hi tortoises. - It's not a God damn race.
当你慢跑  把浑身弄得黏糊糊的时候
While you were jogging getting swamp ass,
我们在分享我们的希望和梦想
we were sharing our hopes and dreams.
没错  我们始终保持满分
That's right, we keep it on the 100.
玛丽  艾琳娜
Marie, Elena,
我们的好邻居彼得昨天帮了大忙
like a good neighbor, Peter was there.
那真是太棒了  老兄
Yeah, that was dope, man.
谢谢你
Thank you.
谢谢你们  这是最起码的
Thank you very much. It's the least I could do.
如果我要盲猜一下
Uh, and if I were to take a shot in the dark,
我猜你马上要成为家庭主妇了
would presume that you are the soon-to-be kept woman.
你上网查过"家庭主妇"这个词吗
Have you ever Googled "Kept woman"?
你熟悉俚语词典吗
You familiar with the Urban Dictionary?
糟了
Oh shit.
对不起  我以为这是...
I'm sorry, I thought that was a--
这是一个好词
that was an okay phrase.
我没有要冒犯你的意思
Um, I--I did not mean to offend you and--
我跟你开玩笑呢
I'm just playing with you.
-好吧  -看见他的脸了吗
- Solid. - Saw his face?
都面无血色了
The blood just drained.
真是个不错的玩笑
That was nice.
我的天  我认识你
Oh my God, I recognize you.
不  我不是艾米·亚当斯[演员]
No, I'm not Amy Adams.
-人们确实...  -不不不
- People do-- - No, no, no.
你是那个主厨
You're that chef.
我在电视上见过你
I seen you on TV.
你有一个节目
You have that show that's, like,
是另一个更有名的厨师的节目的复制版
a facsimile of another show with a more famous chef?
如果你是好意的话  那就谢谢你了
Thank you if you meant that sweetly in any way.
虽然我不这么觉得
And I don't think you did.
但还是要谢谢你认出我来
But still, thank you for recognizing me.
所以你们打算干什么
Um, so what are you guys gonna do?
我们打算留下
We're gonna stay.
就像豪华露营
It's like glamping.
所以你打算勇敢面对了吗
Oh, okay, so you're gonna make some lemonade?
好吧  我们认输了
Okay, well, we thrown in the towel.
她的意思是说  如果我们不回去的话
Translation, if we don't get back,
妈妈和茉根会把我们所有的大麻都吸完
Mom and Morgan will smoke all of our weed.
感谢你的蜡烛  男厨神
Thanks for the fire, Chef Boyardee.
回头见
Check you later.
来吧  别紧张
Come on up and take it easy.
为波多黎各祷告
Pray for Puerto Rico.
-好吧  -一会儿见
- Okay. - See you in a few.
男厨神
Aw, Chef Boyardee.
-还挺有趣的  -所以你跑步吗
- That's funny. - So you, uh, you run?
追人的时候会跑的
When chased, yes.
而且跑得很快
And quickly.
我觉得你在谦虚
I think you're being modest.
这个头巾是不是从你以前最喜欢的衬衫上剪的
That headband didn't cut itself off your favorite old tee.
-这个老东西吗  -是啊
- This old thing? - Mm-hm.
我有个疯狂的想法
Hey, I have a-- I have a crazy idea.
你想让湖结冰  周末我们能在上面打滚吗
You want to freeze the lake so we can curl all weekend?
我确实想这么做
I really do want to do that.
但首先  我想给你
That's a-- but first, I want to cook for you
和你的朋友做顿饭
and your friends.
在你开口之前
Uh, and before you say anything,
我想让你知道
uh, I just want to let you know
你会帮我一个大忙的
you'd be doing me a huge solid
因为在我最畅销的食谱书中
'cause I have, I don't know, three or four recipes I need to work out
有三  四个食谱我需要试验一下
for my new most likely bestselling cookbook.
不是吹牛
Humble brag.
你想让我们在你的大房子里
And you want us as your guinea pigs
-当你的小白鼠  -是的
- in your big fancy house? - Well.
这场理论的盛宴何时开始
What time would this theoretical multi-course feast kick off?
我确实发现
Um, well, I--I do find that
日落配上开胃小菜堪称完美
sunset pairs just perfectly with an amuse-bouche.
什么"小菜"都行  真的
Any "Bouche", really.
*艾格尼丝啊艾格尼丝*
*Ags, Ags, Ags, Ags, Ags, Ags*
*艾格尼丝拿着一个土豆*
*Ags got one potato*
我们得把鞋脱了
Gotta take our shoes off.
我不想把鞋脱了
I don't want to take our shoes off.
你知道我什么意思吗
You know what I mean?
或许这个房子
Maybe it's one of those houses
也是那种你需要脱鞋的房子
where you have to take your shoes off.
-你好啊  -欢迎  女士们
- Hi. - Welcome, ladies.
我想你们会找到充足的电灯
I think you'll find ample electric light.
看看这些白人特权
Oh, look at all this white privilege.
你们自便
Help yourself.
这是我的妈妈  莉莉丝
This is my mom, Lilith.
你好啊
Hello, you, again.
-毕竟你让我的生活充满光彩  -谢谢你
- Well, you lit up my life. - Thank you.
-你帮我戒了烟  -好吧
- You helped me quit smoking. - Oh, well.
你们两个长得真像
You know the family resemblance is striking, you two.
我知道
Oh, I know.
南非大主教
和德斯蒙德·图图的一夜改变了我的生活
Well, one night with Desmond Tutu changed my life forever.
真好笑  你真幽默
That's fun, you're fun.
-我们都很幽默  -是的
- We are fun. - You are.
-这幅画  -我知道
- This painting. - Oh, I know.
我很抱歉  艾格尼丝
I'm sorry-- Agnes?
我让她拿下来  因为这太恐怖了
You know, I asked her to take that down because it is so morbid.
-我喜欢  -我也是
- Oh, I like it. - Me too.
我也喜欢  当你后退一步的时候
I like it. Once you step back, you know,
就好像你让这些层次变得平易近人了
and you kind of let the folksy layers--
你叫我吗
You rang?
艾格尼丝  认识一下我们的客人
Agnes, please meet our guests.
艾格尼丝
Agnes.
她有点像《功夫熊猫》里的阿宝
Ah, she's a bit like Master Po from Kung Fu.
这样可以吗  好的
Is that okay? Good.
你好彼得  我是茉根
Hi Peter, I'm Morgan.
你好
Hello.
玛丽和我在德文郡徒步旅行时相遇
Marie and I met backpacking across Devon.
吃完最后一袋混合干果  我就过来了
Bonded over the last bag of trail mix and here I am.
用高雅的品味来丰富我的婚礼
Supplementing the nups with a touch of class.
-高雅  -这挺好的
- Touch. - Oh, that's nice.
我猜你一定得到了许多
I bet you've got tons of that
尽管你的身材很脆弱
despite your--your fragile stature.
很温馨的家
Lovely home.
谢谢你
Thank you.
从建筑上说
Architecturally speaking.
就风格而言  我不能说我真的喜欢
Style wise, I can't say I really care for it.
充其量算混乱
Muddled at best.
首先  这房子蠢极了
First of all, this house is stupid.
其次  你打不打算给我们吃的
Second, are you gonna feed us or what, papi?
因为你一定不想看见我饥饿的样子
Because you don't want to see me hangry.
都是你们
It's all you guys.
我不行
I can't.
这小东西很好吃
This little things are delicious.
好了
All right.
我要把这发到照片墙上
I've gotta Instagram this.
我会弄一些
And, um, I'm gonna get, like,
椅子套
chair covers.
那叫椅子保温罩
They're called chair cozies.
不不  婚礼椅子保温罩肯定很难看
No, no, wedding chair cozies can't look great.
豆袋坐垫更好
Fuckin' bean bags would be better.
在你们眼里我像梅格汉·马克尔[英国王妃]吗
Do I look like Meghan Markle to y'all?
这就是你为什么应该把婚礼
I mean, that's why you should just have the wedding in,
开在谷仓里的原因
like, a barn of something.
-谷仓  -不  不是真正的谷仓
- A barn? - But not, like, an actual barn.
我的天  忘了我刚才说的
Oh my God, forget I said anything.
彼得  你怎么看待婚礼椅子保温套的
Peter, how do you feel about wedding chair cozies?
-我吗  -是的
- Me? Uh, well... - Yeah.
实话跟你们说
...to be honest with you guys,
我根本不知道你们在说些什么
I have no idea what the gentle fuck you're talkin' about.
但我想知道一下
I want to know more though.
我想知道更多  继续说吧
I want to know more. Keep sharing.
如果你们愿意的话
For those of you willing,
你们接下来要享用的
what you're about to enjoy...
是煎安康鱼
is a pan-seared monkfish.
你们将会看到一些英国豌豆
You'll see some English peas.
很新鲜
Those are fresh.
天啊  太好看了
Oh my gosh, this is beautiful.
看起来像是鳕鱼
I mean, it looks like cod.
它们有相似点
There's a similarity.
艾琳娜
Uh, Elena,
但是它更高端一些
but, um, it's much higher end.
吃吧  吃吧
Y'all, eat up, eat up also,
因为这在他的饭店里很贵
because this is super expensive at his restaurant.
我和他分手的主要原因是
The reason I broke up with him mainly
因为他觉得他有权决定
was because he thought he got to decide
我要不要以及什么时候要孩子
when and if I had babies.
还有盐  对吗
But also the salt, no?
他连培根都要腌制
Also he salted his bacon.
这太难吃了
Oh, that's always gross.
-不是吧  -确实很恶心
- Fuck no. - Yeah, it was grim.
但我爱的人想要决定
But it wasn't as bad as the man I loved
我的身体什么时候改变
wanting to determine
什么时候有新生命从我身体里破壳而出
when my body transforms and bursts forth with...
-这样也不坏  -我的天哪
- suckling young. - Goodness gracious,
你说得好像是《阿基拉》的最后一幕  茉根
you make it sound like the last act of Akira, Morgan.
也没有那么糟
It's not that bad.
抱歉  彼得  你有过孩子吗
I'm sorry, Peter, have you birthed many children?
很遗憾  我还没有
Um, I haven't, unfortunately,
但我见过别人生孩子
but I did see it happen.
我亲自近距离目睹过
Listen, I saw it happen up close and personal,
我感觉如果我有那个小玩意
and I feel like if I had the gadgetry,
我会要孩子的
I would have delivered.
小玩意  大伙儿
The gadgetry, you guys.
不只是生孩子  对吗
You know, it's not just the delivery, right?
是接下来发生的一切
It's everything that comes next
和在那之后的一切
and then everything after that.
你说得对  抱歉  我忘了你想办法
You're right, I'm sorry, I forgot that you managed
略去了分娩的部分
to avoid the pushing part,
你真是太好了  很棒
which is so sweet for you, it's rad.
但我也接受领养  所以...
But I'm also a fan of adoption, so...
我只是说  我不觉得抚养一个小孩
No, I was just saying I don't think raising a child
应该是我们需要优先考虑的一个事
should be another thing we have to prioritize, you know?
这不是负担或是任务
It's not a burden or a task,
只是很简单的一件事
it's just simply what is.
就像呼吸一样  只是你生活的一部分
Becomes as much part of your life as breathing.
但你生活的一部分
But then the parts of your life
你之前觉得是你的生活
that you thought were your life,
比如社交或是创业
like socializing or career building,
探索及表达艺术
and, you know, exploring or expressing art,
这些事驱动你  定义你
those things that drove you and defined you,
所有的这些选项都没被选中
all those boxes get left unchecked.
当然他们还是很重要
Of course they still matter.
你们希望你的孩子长大之后
And you want your child to grow up
不仅仅是想当一名母亲
and see more than just Mom.
你想让他们成为一名梦想家或是爱人
You want them to see a dreamer and a lover
或是企业家之类的
and an entrepreneur or whatever.
你想让他们成为
You want them to see...
你
you.
或许会受到鼓舞
And maybe be inspired.
我的天  母亲节是什么时候  五月吗
Oh my God, when is Mother's Day, May?
该死
Fuck.
我成为了你
I see you.
我爱你
I love you.
这真是温馨的一幕
Well, that is a cockle warmer.
没感觉吗
No, nothing?
气氛很僵硬啊
Tough room.
各位  拜托  我开玩笑的
Guys, come on, I'm kidding.
我开玩笑的
I'm kidding.
这是一段美妙的独白  莉莉丝
That was a beautiful soliloquy, Lilith,
我觉得我们应该为此喝一杯
and I think that we should all drink to it.
我的天  彼得
Oh my God, Peter.
我的老天
Oh my goshness.
我让自己变得尴尬了
I've just embarrassed myself.
-幸亏你抓住了  -没事的
- Well--well caught. - It's okay.
我也很好奇
I'm also very curious
这是什么东西
as to what is-- what is that about?
这有点吸引我
That's intriguing.
这是什么
What this is about?
姐妹情谊
Sisterhood.
凯尔特风格  我说的对吗女士们
Celtic style, am I right, ladies?
那是2015年的狂欢节
It was about Mardi Gras 2015.
当时是羊年
Year of the motherfuckin' goat.
我喜欢我们的纹身
Oh, I love our tattoos.
我也是
Yeah, me too.
天啊  有人也出汗吗  像偷了东西一样
Oh, whoa, is anybody else sweating like they stole something?
艾琳娜  你怎么这么热
Elena, how are you hot?
-我不知道  -她总是这样
- I don't know. - She always is.
*去睡觉吧*
*Go to sleep*
*在掩盖之下*
*Underneath the cover*
外面有你喜欢的吗
See anything out there you like?
作为雇主对女佣说
Well, uh, speaking man to matron,
我可以说
I-- I could say
外面没有我不喜欢的
there's nothing out there I don't like.
你可真是包容啊
How inclusive of you.
谢谢你
Thank you.
但是实话实说
Truthfully, though,
我感觉我有点不会使用厨具了
I am feeling kind of invisible to housewares.
明智而不含糊其辞的话可能会有所帮助
Huh, wiser words without slurring might help.
或许别再瞎说八道了
Maybe stop spilling shit.
你的诚实没有底线  艾格尼丝
Your honesty is boundary free, Ags.
而我是真的醉了
And I am tipsy.
天啊  吃点东西吧
Eat something, for Christ's sake.
好
Well, sure.
悠着点  我不会替你收拾你的烂摊子了
Go easy, I'm not gonna clean up any more of your messes.
-给你  -谢谢你
- Here. - Thank you.
谢谢你  又加热了一遍
Thank you, mm, reheated.
顺便说一句  我很喜欢你和你的粥
BTDubs, I'm a big fan of you and your porridge.
-我喜欢  -谢了
- I like that. - Yeah, thanks.
你上次正经和姑娘们一起潇洒是什么时候了
Yeah, when is the last time you had a solid girls' night out?
我觉得你该出去
I feel like you should get out there,
告诉她们关于埃莉诺·罗斯福的八卦
tell 'em some shit about Eleanor Roosevelt,
你懂我的意思吗
you know what I'm saying?
也许跟她们说说第一个吸尘器的故事
Maybe tell 'em the story of the first vacuum.
你真是个傻子
You're an idiot.
*面具之下*
*Underneath the cover*
真是太好听了
That's-- that's gorgeous.
谁想要奶油或牛奶
Anybody need cream or milk?
就告诉我
Just let me know.
我的天  艾格尼丝
My gosh, Agnes!
你都忙一天了
You've been on your feet all day.
不如你坐会歇歇
Why don't you sit down, take a load off?
也许传授点知识
Maybe drop some knowledge.
我太老了  传授什么都不好使了
I'm too old to be dropping anything.
我只是很享受看到姐妹们团聚
I'm just enjoying the festivities watching some sisters commune.
她来了
Oh, there she is.
选举权
Suffrage.
我的最爱
My day.
都不喜欢吗  好吧
No? Okay.
其实你们都很幸运
Truth is, you all are lucky.
女人互相依靠并不是件易事
Wasn't always this easy for women to lean on each other.
在那个时代
There was a time when it...
没有人在意女人的心声
wasn't about choosing to be heard,
因为你无法发声
because you had no voice.
如果不曾拥有  又如何使用
How can you use something you were never given?
女人遭受的痛苦都会在你们心中留下烙印
Something terrible happens to a woman and it just lives in you.
在她心中
In her.
首先侵蚀你的内心  然后蔓延至皮肤
Starts on the inside and then it becomes her skin
直到她死去  都会留有印记
and she wears it till she dies and that's that.
刚才她只是在热身  姑娘们
And that was just her tight five, ladies.
等着看今年秋天Hulu台特别节目上映吧
Wait, just wait until her Hulu special drops this fall.
我为女士们做了巧克力
I made chocolate things for women.
-请别一下子...  -谢了  老兄
- Please don't all just... - I'm good, bro.
-好  -也许等会吧  谢了  彼得
- Yeah. - Maybe later, Peter. Thanks.
看上去像野花
They look like wild flavors.
对  没错
Oh, yeah. Yes.
你还好吗  彼得
You all right over there, Pete?
还行
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
我就是  也许酒喝多了
I just-- I maybe had a little too much to drink
吃的太少
and not enough to eat.
这就是  就是厨师的诅咒
This is the-- this is the chef's curse.
恕我失陪一下
Hey, I'll bid you excuse me.
恕我不奉陪
I'll bid you adieu.
你们想待多久都行
Um, stay as long as you like, okay?
如果愿意可以住下来
Stay the night if you like.
午夜时分我可以来点侧卧相拥
I will be available for some light spooning during the witching hour,
只要我可以做外侧的那个人
as long as I can be the big spoon.
彼得  很感谢你的好意
Peter, your hospitality is greatly appreciated.
谢谢你和艾格尼丝做的美味晚餐
Thank you and Agnes for such a delicious meal.
我有重力
I had this gravity.
那里有台阶
There's a step there.
-晚安  -好
- Good night. - Okay.
谢谢
Thank you.
你好啊
Cheerio.
幸好还活着
Well, that's good.
我们喝了多少酒
Hey, how much did we drink?
好吧
Okay.
*两个姐妹肩并肩*
*There were two sisters side by side*
*唱吧傻瓜  整日吟唱*
*Sing aye dumb, sing aye day*
*两个姐妹肩并肩*
*There were two sisters side by side*
*这些男孩为我而生*
*The boys are born for me*
*两个姐妹肩并肩*
*There were two sisters side by side*
*爱哭小约翰和姐姐一对*
*The eldest for young Johnny cried*
行  我去看看
Okay, I'll bite.
*我会对爱人忠心不二*
*I'll be true unto my love*
*若他对我真心*
*If he'll be true to me*
*约翰给妹妹买了一个大金戒*
*Johnny bought the youngest a big gold ring*
*唱吧傻瓜  整日吟唱*
*Sing aye dumb, sing aye day*
*约翰给妹妹买了一个大金戒*
*Johnny bought the youngest a big gold ring*
*这些男孩为我而生*
*The boys are born for me*
你好啊  格洛里奥
Well, hey there, Glorio.
我喜欢你的外套  但是
I do like your outfit, but...
你在这干什么
why are you here?
你是来借宿
Are you a boarder
还是只是探望艾格尼丝
or are you just visiting Agnes?
我去把那个关了
I'm gonna turn that down
因为太难听
'cause it sucks.
*若他对我真心*
*If he'll be true to me*
*约翰为妹妹买了顶海狸帽*
*Johnny bought the youngest a beaver hat*
*唱吧傻瓜*
*Sing aye dumb*♪
天
Sh...
不
Fuck no.
茉根  太阳照屁股了
Hey Morgan, rise and shine, please.
操
Fuck!
我很确定艾格尼丝
I'm pretty sure that Agnes
崇拜孔雀和魔鬼
worships peacocks and the devil.
茉根  是你吗
Morgan, is that you?
彼得  帮帮我
Peter, help me.
茉根
Morgan!
该死
Goddammit.
见鬼
False!
茉根  从你那边拉门
Morgan, pull--pull on your side of the door, please.
我在拉
I'm pulling.
茉根
Morgan?
快开门
Open the goddamned door!
我开不了  锁上了
I can't, it's locked!
彼得  帮帮我  我好害怕
Peter, help me, I'm scared.
该死
Oh, shit!
彼得  你还在吗
Peter? Are you still there?
茉根  有点不对劲
Morgan, something's wrong.
我动不了
I can't move!
茉根  醒醒
Morgan, wake up!
我觉得我瘫痪了
I think I'm paralyzed.
天哪  彼得
Oh, God... Peter.
我在哪
Where am I?
看着我  不不
Look at me. No, no, no.
看着我  看我  别回头
Look at, look at-- do not turn around.
我的天
Oh my God.
天哪  我的天
Oh my... oh my God!
什么
What?
彼得  彼得  爱吃南瓜
Peter, Peter, pumpkin eater.
家有娇妻却留不住她
Had a wife but couldn't keep her,
因为他是个调皮的坏男孩
because he'd been a very, very bad boy.
什么情况
What the fuck?
干得好  茉根
Well-done, Morgan.
不  接下来交给我吧
No, I think I can probably take it from here.
坚强点  哥们
Stiff upper lip, mate.
真是段倒霉的日子
It's been a deuce of a time.
-谢谢  -谢谢你
- Thank you. - Thank you.
彼得
Peter.
我没法想象
I just can't imagine
现在你心里的想法
what's running through your head right now.
无需想像  我可以直接告诉你
Oh, you don't need to, I can tell you, it's, uh,
"为什么我他妈的动不了"
"Why can't I move my fuckin' body"
还有"赶紧把这个项圈从我脖子上摘了"
and "Get this collar off me fuckin' now."
别爆粗口
Language!
你以为自己是谁
Who do you think you are?
我以为自己是谁
Who do you think I am?
我很意外你没认出我  彼得
I'd say I'm surprised you don't recognize me, Peter,
但说实话  上次见你时我还是个孩子
but to be fair, I was a child the last time you were around.
不过大家都说  我和我姐长得一模一样
Still, everyone says I'm the spitting image of my sister, and, well,
我知道你肯定记得她
I know you remember her.
我完全不知道你在说什么
I have no idea who you're talking about.
惠勒
Wheeler.
卡拉·惠勒
Kara Wheeler.
你是贝卡的妹妹
You're Becca's sister?
曾是
Was.
原来这些疯狂举动都是为了她
So that's what all this insanity is about.
她是自杀的
She took the easy way out.
这还是我的错
It's my fault?
你姐姐的死是一场悲剧
What happened to your sister is tragic.
真的
Truly.
也非常懦弱
It's also fuckin' cowardly.
不是吗  你的父母怎么办
Right? What about your parents?
你怎么办
What about you?
还有海洛因
And then the heroin.
海洛因  卡拉
The fuckin' heroin, Kara.
拜托  我知道你很生气
Come on, I know you're angry.
你想要些安慰  但这个
You want some closure, but this,
这样你得不到慰藉
this is not the way to get it.
这样你将面临十到二十年的牢狱之灾
This... this is how you get 10 to 20.
你知道是我发现了她的尸体吗
Did you know I was the one that found her?
她用了你的烹饪刀  彼得
She used a knife from your line of cutlery, Peter.
就是在你的狗屁电视节目上出售的那种
The very set you sell on your piece-of-shit TV show.
你以为那是个巧合吗
Do you think that was a coincidence?
当时我们只是青少年  卡拉
We were teenagers, okay, Kara?
无论你以为发生了什么
And whatever you're thinking,
该死  我保证
fuck, I guarantee you
事情不是那样  好吗
that's not what happened, all right?
时间正好
Right on cue.
-好样的  -该死
- All right. - Shit.
好
Okay.
那是什么玩意
Uh, what the hell is that?
别担心  还没装上弓呢
Don't worry, it's not loaded.
现在装上了
Right, then, now that it's loaded,
如果我是你  我就会担心
I would be worried, if I were you.
什么玩意
What the fuck?
我了个去
Holy shit.
你看上去很紧张  彼得
You seem tense, Peter.
说得好  老大
Way to represent, OG.
这样也不坏
Suckling young.
天啊
Oh my God.
好吧  你们都是疯子
Okay, okay, okay, so you are all crazy,
你们都疯了
you're all just crazy,
你们的大脑有问题
and your brains are sick,
你们会因此受到惩罚的
and you're not gonna get away with this,
你们这些愤怒的婊子
you... angry bitches!
彼得
Oh, Peter.
我们不是愤怒的婊子
We're not angry bitches.
我们是愤怒的女巫
We're angry witches.
艾格尼丝
Agnes!
你对我做了什么
What did you do to me?
瘫痪
The paralysis.
这是个补充咒  但总是很有效
It's a remedial spell but always quite effective.
容我失陪一下  彼得
Now, if you'll excuse me, Peter,
一个女人总有很多事要做
a woman's work is never, ever done.
艾格尼丝
Agnes!
救救我
Help me!
给自己留点自尊  小瘦子
Have some self-respect, Slim.
你们在干什...
What are you...
你们在计划什么
What are you planning?
你们在干什...
What are you...
你们怎么回事
Hey, what is your deal, even... huh?
那是什么  那是什么
Yeah? What is that-- what is that--
你们刚才交换的那个眼神
what is that nonverbal cue, huh?
你们根本没在帮我
You guys aren't helping me at all, please.
我们不能让你这样出来
We can't let you go out like this.
出门
Out?
别害怕
Don't sweat it.
我们要打理一下你
We're gonna tighten you up.
你们要帮我打理
You're gonna tighten me up,
什么打理  打理什么
what is tighten-- tighten what up?
所有一切
All of it.
拜托
Oh, come on.
别动
Shh, stay very still.
不  不不  不能这样了
No! No, no, this stops now.
*闭嘴闭嘴闭嘴闭嘴*
*Shut, shut, shut, shut*
*闭上你的臭嘴*
*Shut your fucking mouth*
*没人想听你的废话*
*No one wants to hear your bullshit*
*闭上你的臭嘴*
*Shut your fucking mouth*
-不  不  -天哪
- No! No. - Oh, boy.
不错
That's good.
不
No.
天哪
Oh, God.
操
Oh, f...
该死
Oh, shit!
毒蛇给蛇蝎
Snake for snake.
你们都不认识我
You don't even know me.
你们不认识我  你们只知道
You don't know me, all you know is
搜索引擎里读到的那些
what you read in the search engine.
非常感谢能给我这个独家采访
Thank you so much for this exclusive.
说实话  我是你的忠实粉丝
Confession? I'm a big fan,
但这采访只是工作
But this is just business.
阿谀奉承能给你开很多门
Well, flattery'll get you everywhere.
我的工作就是我的快乐之源
My business is my pleasure.
这是什么
What is this?
-好极了  -没错
- Um... great. - Yeah!
那我们开始吧
So let's get started, okay.
你与食物
When did your love affair
何时结下了情缘
with food start?
不如你直接问我你真正想问的问题
Why don't you ask me what you really wanna ask me?
我不知道你什么意思
I don't know what you mean.
好吧  我操了  别这样
Okay, fuck no, you guys, come on.
你们是一家人  老天
You're family, for Christ's sake.
这简直错得太离谱了  怎么
This is wrong on so many levels, what it--
怎么回事
what is happening?
别  我们能不能
Oh-- oh please, can we just,
能不能就专注采访
stick to the interview?
别装了  这就是采访
Come on, this is the interview.
听着  我...
Look, I--I...
我们能不能专业点
can we just keep it on the level?
-好啊  -我真的不喜欢
- Yeah, yeah. - I'm really not comfortable
-你这样...  -好吧好吧
- with where this is-- - Okay, okay, hey.
真的吗
Seriously?
你争取这个独家新闻多久了
How long you been chasing this exclusive?
你到底写给谁看
I mean, who the fuck do you write for?
有谁读你这玩意  拜托
Who's reading this shit? Come on.
不不  你们这些混蛋
No, no, no, no, you assholes.
我是你成名的机会  我是你成名的机会
I'm your brass ring. I'm your brass ring.
不不  事情不是这样的
No, that's not how it happened.
事情不是这样的
That's not how it happened.
你们能不能消停会
This-- can you please cut that out?
别演了
Cut--cut that out.
贱人
Ow! Cunt!
你他妈咬了我
You fucking bit me!
暂停
Unquote.
她根本不想和你上床  彼得
She don't wanna fuck you, Peter.
虽然她是你的粉丝
Just because she's a fan of your work
但不意味着你能碰她
doesn't mean you get to touch her.
这里  或者这里
Here, or here...
不可以
It's not okay.
从来都不可以
It's never been okay.
看看奶子
Look at the tits.
看看奶子  兄弟
Check the tits, bro.
不如我告诉你们疯女人
Hey, how about a giant obvious newsflash
一个显而易见的道理
for you two certifiable loony bins:
每个故事都有两面  懂吗
There's two sides to every story, okay?
她为了这个独家新闻争取了好几周
She chased that exclusive for weeks.
-她在酒吧和我见面  -是你让她去的
- She met me at a bar. - You told her to meet you there!
她带了一个录音笔
She brought a recorder
和一个笔记薄
and a fucking legal pad!
一整晚她都在拼命和我调情
She flirted her ass off with me the whole time.
之后她竟然还有胆咬我
And then, she had the balls to bite me,
因为她就是个疯婆子
because she was a crazy bitch!
你想见识下真正疯狂的东西吗
You wanna see something really fucking crazy?
老天
Oh boy.
怎么回事
What's happening?
你惹女巫生气了  彼得
You pissed off a witch, Peter.
-而且玛丽还是伏都教  所以  -该死
- And Marie fucks with voodoo, so... - Oh, shit.
天哪  天哪  救救我  救救我吧
Oh God. Oh God, help me. Please, please help me.
还不行  玛丽
Not yet, Marie.
时候未到
It's too soon.
-他自找的  -我知道
- He fucking asked for it. - I have no doubt.
你现在是真的时日无多了
You are officially on borrowed time.
天哪  快看
Oh boy, look at that.
看看你干的好事
Look what you did.
你尿床了
You pissed yourself.
现在你只能躺在自己的尿里
Now you're gonna have to lay there in your own sauce
而我还得闻着
and I'm gonna have to smell it.
但你还是很幸运
Still, you're lucky.
我本不会阻止她
I wouldn't have stopped her.
她的烈性子简直让我神魂颠倒
All that spitfire just makes me melt.
不然我为什么向她求婚呢
Why do you think I asked her to marry me?
她就是我的梦中情人
She checks all my boxes.
-真恶心  -不好意思
- That is disgusting. - Oh, I'm sorry.
这个对你来说太重口了吗
Is that a bridge too far?
该死  所以一切都是谎言吗
Oh, shit! So it's just all lies, huh?
天哪  你都没有孩子
God, you don't even have a kid.
别傻了
Don't be ridiculous.
我女儿去年以优异成绩毕业
My daughter graduated cum laude last year,
还是在那次袭击之后
and that was after the assault.
幸运的是  那个禽兽还能如鱼得水
Luckily, that monster was still able to play in a bowl game.
丝毫没有受到任何影响
Hasn't seemed to have affected his draft status one bit.
感谢上帝她有勇气站出来
Thank God she had the courage to come forward.
你在想什么
What are you thinking?
给你敷上
There we go.
等待第二幕
Stick around for act two.
到那时我们再阉了你
That's when we castrate you.
不准偷看
No peeking!
你好啊
¡Hola!
真是个
That's a nice--
这颜色真不错
that's a nice color.
我很高兴你喜欢
Oh, I'm so glad you like it!
我们觉得这颜色很配你的肤色
We thought it would look good with your skin tone.
你准备好变身为漂亮彼得了吗
You ready to become Pretty Peter?
你准备好戴着手铐脚链回菲律宾了吗
Are you excited to head back to the Philippines in shackles?
这个混球  你知道我是波多黎各人
Wow. This motherfucker-- you know I'm Puerto Rican!
你想谈谈手铐吗
You wanna talk about shackles?
当波多黎各还是西班牙殖民地时
You know, when Puerto Rico was still a Spanish colony,
根本没有女权这一说
women's rights were unheard of
而她们对岛上的社会贡献非常受限
and their contributions to the island's society were limited,
委婉地说
to put it mildly.
尽管波多黎各女人积极参与
Even though Puerto Rican women were actively participating
反抗西班牙人
in the revolt against the Spaniards,
但没人比西班牙人更擅长强奸和掠夺
and nobody can rape and pillage like the Spanish,
不是吗
am I right?
放松
Relax.
我在给你上妆
I'm just texturizing.
-你能撅嘴吗  -你能食屌吗
- Will you pout, please? - Will you eat a dick?
好粗鲁
That's rude.
信不信由你
Believe it or not,
我可是个正宗的美国人
I'm as American as apple-motherfucking-pie.
我的曾祖母为国而战
My great-grandmother served our great country
与希特勒和他的盟军打仗
in the war against Hitler and his allies.
多么爱国啊
What a patriot!
我很抱歉这份勇气没遗传给你
I'm sorry that the courage skipped your generation.
但我感激她的奉献  真的
But I am grateful for her service, truly.
是吗
Are you?
就像你很感激
The way you're grateful for the service of,
你的女性员工的付出吗
I don't know, your female kitchen staff?
你听说过同工同酬吗
You ever hear of equal pay for equal work,
你这个垃圾
you pasty piece of shit?
你睡过多少个手下
And how many of them have you slept with, huh?
包括你开除的那个
Including the one you fired.
玛塔·多明戈斯
Marta Dominguez.
单亲妈妈  两个孩子
Single mother of two,
不过在你看来  这个世界已经有
and that was enough brown babies for this world,
够多的棕色宝宝了
as far as you were concerned.
这是我们共同的决定
Yeah, we came to that decision together.
共同
Together?
那为什么要给封口费
Then why settle?
你给了她两万吧
That one cost you 20 grand.
为一个员工花这么多钱可是大手笔
Big money for one of your employees.
你不该这样做吧  茉根
Isn't this beneath you, Morgan?
你们不是发明礼仪的吗
Didn't you people invent manners?
他是说英国
He means the English.
这些都不是从那儿传过来的
None of this shit flies across the Pond.
这些都是美式最下作的手段
This is strictly American awfulness at its worst.
首先  彼得
First of all, Peter,
你这辈子做的下作事
the utter shite that you've been doing
基本堪比全球性的霍乱了
your entire life is part of an international pandemic.
-说得好  -第二
- Ooh, good word. - Yeah. And second,
你知道该死的巫术
do you know a thing about fuckin' witchcraft
和该死的起源吗
and its fuckin' origins?
拜托  我...我想和你进行正常的交流
Nice. Come on, I'm... trying to talk to you like a human,
但你却嘲讽我  还想个恶霸一样
and you're mocking me and you're wrapping your finger
把手指扣在扳机上
around a trigger like a bully.
你害怕的时候真的很无能
You're a real wanker when you're frightened,
你知道吗
do you know that?
我的确很害怕  茉根
Yeah, I'm frightened, Morgan.
我很害怕  因为我被绑架了  而且
I'm scared, 'cause I've been kidnapped and...
被陌生人
accused,
指控  定罪  处刑  我...
and convicted and sentenced by strangers, and I--
我有一个叫莱利的女儿
I have a daughter named Riley.
但是  彼得
Yeah, but Peter,
摧毁现有的规则就会带来巨大的改变
great change comes with the destruction of existing rules.
什么
What?
我妹妹的皮肤和我一样
My sister's skin is my own,
我妹妹的心和我一样
my sister's heart is my own,
我妹妹的未来和我一样
and my sister's future is my own.
该死  她还是个新人
Oh, shit, she's in training, huh?
这是你第一次  对吗
This is your first time, isn't it?
做梦去吧
In your dreams.
不  我现在可不是做梦
No, not in my dreams, right now.
我了解你
I know you.
我和你一起长大
I grew up with you.
茉根
Morgan.
你就像是我的妹妹
You're just like my sister.
你渴望被人所接受
You're desperate for acceptance.
我有个哥哥
I have a brother.
他会做奶酪洋葱三明治
He makes cheese-and-onion sandwiches
他们就爱到发狂
and they're the tits.
他的鞋子就是擦不亮
You still couldn't shine his shoes.
是谁摧毁了你的自尊
Who was it that destroyed your self-esteem so completely
让你愿意
that you are willing
加入有史以来都烂的姐妹会
to pledge the worst sorority in history?
是你爸爸吗
Was it your dad?
够了  蠢蛋
That's enough, pendejo.
每个混蛋都会说
Every asshole says he's an asshole
因为爸爸是混蛋所以自己才变成混蛋
because his father was an asshole.
别被他的话迷惑了
No te dejes que te meta en la cabeza.
这只是他的把戏
It's just dead skin.
茉根  拜托
Morgan, come on.
这辈子为你自己
Make one decision for yourself
-决定一次  -操你妈的
- in your life. - Fuck you!
你对我的这辈子一点都不了解
You know nothing about my life!
欢迎加入我们  贱人
Welcome to the fucking game, bitch!
该死
Oh, shit!
星号  六  九
Star... six... nine.
-喂  -朗尼  我是彼得
- Hello? - Lonnie-- Lonnie, it's Peter.
我被女巫们绑架了
I'm a hostage of witches.
我报过警了  打不通  你能相信...
I tried 911 already, it's busy, can you believe--
你这样只会让你自己更痛苦  彼得
You just made this a lot more painful for yourself, Peter.
朗尼
Lonnie?
我是叫这个名字  别忘了
That's my name, don't wear it out.
天啊  这么晚了  你真是
God, it's so late, you freaked me out there
吓了我一跳
for a second.
没错
Right.
我不住在这里的
I don't live here.
彼得邀请我们几位女士来共进晚餐
Peter invited us ladies over for dinner.
我们没电了  他可怜我们
Our power went out and he took pity on us.
彼得给我店里打了个电话
Peter called me at the shop,
他听起来很惊慌
he sounded pretty shook up.
朗尼  彼得没事
Lonnie, Peter's fine.
他只是骗你的
He was just yanking your chain.
就像我们小时候那样
Like when we were kids?
-但是我们不是小孩子了  -他是个恶霸  朗尼
- Oh, but we're not kids anymore. - He was a bully, Lonnie.
我很遗憾  他之前一直都让你觉得你...
I'm sorry if he ever made you feel like you were--
很蠢吗
Dumb?
-我不蠢  -我知道
- I'm not dumb. - I know you're not.
如果你真的指望我相信
Hmm, you probably should turned more lights on,
你们在里面共进晚餐
if you really wanted me to believe
那你们最好多开点灯
that you were inside having supper.
我要进去看一看
I'll come in and take a look around.
朗尼
Lonnie...
回家吧  孩子
Go home, boy.
-这与你无关  -母亲
- This doesn't concern you. - Mother...
交给我吧  回床上去
I got this handled, go on back to bed.
我和你怎么说的来着
What did I tell you about that thing, huh?
我怎么说的
What'd I say?
这里有点不对劲
Something's not right here.
-你爱你的母亲吗  -当然了
- You love your mother? - 'Course I do.
好吧
All right.
那就收好这个  回家
Then you take this and you go home.
一切都在掌控之中
Everything's under control.
你忘记你自己来过这里
You just forget you were ever here.
你出现的时机正好
Your timing is impeccable.
彼得知道吗
Does Peter know?
彼得和格温自己当时都只是孩子
Peter and Gwen were just babies themselves.
你为什么要保守这个秘密
Why'd you have to keep it a secret?
因为苹果不会落到离树很远的地方
Because the apple doesn't fall far from the tree.
天啊
Oh my God.
彼得的父亲
Peter's father?
回去了结你自己挑起的事
Go back in there and finish what you started.
不要再搞砸了
And no more fuck-ups.
伙计  搞什么
Hey, man. What the fuck?
这可不大好
That was enlightening.
把钥匙给我  交给我
Gimme the keys, I'll take care of it.
猎枪给我
I'll call shotgun.
这都没必要
None of that will be necessary.
真的吗
Oh, oh, really?
跟我的额头说去
Tell that to my fucking forehead.
我们应该施更强的咒语
We should've cast a stronger spell.
我们低估了你
We actually underestimated you.
笼内训练结束了
Crate training's over.
布谷  布谷
Oh, cuckoo, cuckoo!
-这配色真不错  -我喜欢
- What a beautiful color. - Yeah, I like the way
你穿这件衣服后立起来的奶头  宝贝
your titties look in that top, baby.
有必要吗
Look, really?
穿你妹妹的衣服
Your sister's clothes?
她不是已经入土了吗
I mean, isn't she rolling in her grave?
我们要进行女巫捕猎
We're going on a witch hunt.
你懂吗  层次不一样
You get it? Levels.
应该是我们来捕猎你
It's really more of us hunting you
而不是你捕猎我们
as opposed to you hunting us.
对经典的反转
It's a twist on an old classic.
走吧  外国佬
Vámonos, gringo. -
来  跑吧
Come on, jog on!
快跑  彼得
Go, Pe-ter!
我能直接射他吗
Can I just shoot him in the bollocks?
-快跑  彼得  -拜托
- Go Peter, go! Oh! Come on!
拜托  拜托
Please, please.
不要这样  她的在天之灵看着呢
Please stop this. She had a soul.
-十  -你还是快跑吧  小伙子
- Ten... - You better run, boy.
好吧  抱歉
Hey! Okay, sorry.
九
Nine...
-好吧  -八
- Okay. - Eight...
-快跑  彼得  -七
- Go Peter, go! - Seven...
该死
Sh-- shit.
著名厨师丑闻  十名女记者提出性侵指控
玛塔·多明戈斯
Marta Dominguez.
火焰亦是欲火
厨师彼得面临性侵指控
她根本不想和你上床  彼得
She don't wanna fuck you...
彼得
Peter.
当时我们只是青少年
We were teenagers,
好吗
okay?
救命  救命
Help! Help!
救救我
Help me!
救命  该死
Help me! Hel-- Oh, shit!
格温  格温  等等
Gwen! Gwen! Gwen! Wait!
-谢天谢地  是你  -彼得  怎么...
- Oh thank God, it's you! - Peter, what is--
该死  快走  快走
Fuck! Go, go, go!
-彼得  你...  -快开车  格温  快开
- Peter, what-- - Fuckin' drive, Gwen, fuckin' drive!
-好吧  -该死
- Okay, okay! - Shit!
你要告诉我是怎么回事吗
Are you gonna tell me what's going on?
你穿的是什么东西
What the hell are you wearing?
有一群女巫折磨我
Fuckin' bitch witches tortured me.
她们绑架了我
Fuckin' took me hostage.
她们给我的腿施法  格温
The put a spell on my limbs, Gwen!
该死  她们剪去了我的头发
Goddamn, they took my hair,
取走了我的血
took my blood.
她们在我脸上化妆  盯着我的脸
They put makeup on my face, look at my face!
慢点  好吗  你...
Slow down, okay? Just--
我没法慢点  格温
I can't slow down, Gwen.
她们把贝卡的自杀怪在我头上
They're blaming me for Becca's suicide.
对
Yeah.
你知道卡拉吗  她的妹妹
You know Kara, her sister?
她就是女杀人魔  她是领头的
Well, she's the lady Manson, she's the ringleader.
她们一直在跟踪我
And they've been following me,
她们知道我的一些非常非常深的秘密
and they know some deep, deep personal secrets.
她们正在跟踪我  我们得赶紧走
They're stalking me and we need to go,
我们得赶紧去找警察
and we need to go to the cops now.
操
Oh, fuck!
她们要把我的屌切了
They were gonna cut my dick off.
操
Fuck!
她们会修复好你  不是解决你
I said they could fix you, not "Fix" You.
你刚刚说什么
What in the living shit did you just say to me?
你听得很清楚
You heard me.
这都是你干的
You did this to me?
-格温  -我也不想的
- Gwen-- - I didn't want to!
好吗  但是你让我别无选择
Okay? But you just-- you left me no choice,
因为历史又一次重演了
because it's happening all over again, and--
没错  你继续难受吧
Oh yeah, you better be upset.
因为你让我留下了一辈子的阴影
'Cause you have scarred me for life
你可是我的妹妹
and you are my goddamned sister!
没错  你就是在我们的树屋里
Yeah, I was your sister when you raped my best friend
强奸了我最好的朋友
in our fucking treehouse!
强奸  你说我"强奸"
Rape? Did you just say "Rape" To me?
上帝啊  格温  我都不知道
Holy shit, Gwen, I don't even know
这个词到底是什么意思
what that fuckin' word means anymore.
没有人知道  好吗
Nobody does, okay?
我们当时还是孩子
We were kids.
我才十几岁  我喝醉了
I was a teenager, I was drunk,
我光着身子  那感觉都是上辈子的事了
I was fuckin' naked, it was a blurry mess
一片模糊
that happened a lifetime ago!
不  对你来说是一片模糊  彼得
No, it's a blurry mess to you, Peter.
对你来说是上辈子的事
It's a lifetime ago to you!
-我说了  我醉了  -不
- Like I said, I was drunk. - No!
不  你永远有借口  彼得
No, you always have an excuse, Peter,
你永远能逃脱
and you always get away with it,
不仅仅是贝卡
and it is not just with Becca,
因为还有太多其他受害者
because there have been too many others,
那个几年前
what about the journalist that interviewed you
采访你的记者呢  你对她做了什么
a few years ago, right? Hm, what did you do to her?
彼得  或者你的那个员工
Huh, Peter? Or the women on your staff,
或者你的律师
or the new one that your lawyer's
最近在给你处理的那个
fixing for you right now, what were the--
这次的辞退令是怎么写的
what were the marching orders this time?
"她来面试真人秀
Is it "Oh, she auditioned for a reality show,
那她肯定是个拜金的婊子"  对吗
so she just must be a gold-digging whore," Right?
这不是你们公司的信条吗
Isn't that the company line?
你伤害了贝卡
You hurt Becca
没有人相信她的说法
and no one believed her story,
因为你那么完美  彼得
because you were perfect, Peter,
你说她是骗子  于是她就变成了骗子
and you called her a liar, so that's what she was.
后来  她就慢慢被吞噬了
And over time, it just ate her alive.
我维护你
And I defended you
是因为你是我的哥哥
because you're my brother,
不是因为我相信你  我不信
not because I believed you, because I didn't.
这就是我要背负的罪孽
And that's just my cross to bear.
好吧  你...
Yeah, okay, you're...
你说得对
you're right.
对不起
I'm sorry.
你得赶紧开车  赶紧开车走
You have to drive right now. You have to drive right now!
她们是该死的女巫
They're fuckin' witches!
-她们没告诉你她们是女巫吗  -彼得  别说了
- Did they tell you they're fuckin' witches?   -No, Peter! Stop it!
听听你自己说的话
Listen to yourself!
搞什么  好吧
What the fuck? Okay.
她们没和我说过这个
They did not say anything about that.
-我要打给卡拉  -不  不要
- I'm gonna call Kara, and-- - No-- no, don't!
那就是卡拉
That's Kara!
不  不
No! No!
彼得  救我  彼得  彼得
Peter, help me! Peter! Peter!
格温  格温
Gwen! Gwen!
我...我的手
Oh, my... my hands...
不  不
No! No!
不
Ah! No!
Noo!
格温  你在吗
Gwen, are you here?
早上好  亲爱的
Good morning, dear.
-我妹妹呢  -你真好
- Where's my sister? - That's sweet.
格温在自己的床上醒来
Gwen woke up in her own bed.
她不会记得在这里发生的事  所以
She'll have no memory of what happened here, so
除非你想让她或者其他人
unless you want her or anyone else, for that matter,
认为你应该被送进精神病院
to think you belong in an asylum,
我建议你把我们之间的小小冒险
I suggest you take our little adventure
带入坟墓  永不再提
with you to the grave.
你对我做了什么
What did you do to me?
为了贝卡
For Becca.
如果你再干坏事
You fuck up once,
你再想要伤害任何人
you even think of hurting anyone ever again,
我们就埋了你
we will bury you.
你根本预料不到
You'll never see it coming.
明白了吗
Are we clear?
好的  女士
Yes, ma'am.
谢谢
Thank you.
我们会盯着你  彼得
We'll be watching, Peter.
真简单
Well, that was easy.
他斯德哥尔摩综合征了吗
Stockholm syndrome, anyone?
他说谢谢
He said thank you.
-真老套  -钉子
- That was clutch. - Stakes.
电击器
Charges?
绝对在白天就得喝一杯了
Definitely day drinking, right?
上帝啊
Jesus!
不错的派对小把戏
A hell of a party trick.
的确很不错
Yeah, it's pretty good.
保持手机开机
Keep your phone on.
他会给你打电话
He'll call you.
不是马上  但是
Not right away, but...
-他会打来的  -好的
- he'll call. - Right.
顺便  你做得很好
You nailed that, by the way.
天啊
Oh my God.
我真的超级担心他会
I was so nervous that he was gonna
突然跳出车外  或者把我推出车外
jump out of the car or push me out of the car
让我们没法演下去
before we got to the spot.
然后我...我就失控了
Then I just... I lost my shit.
我  我真的失控了
I mean, I really lost it.
你是完美的压轴
You were the perfect closer.
我真的很抱歉  卡拉
I'm so sorry, Kara.
我每天都在想她
I think about her every single day.
我也是
Yeah, me too.
天啊  真的很对不起
Oh, God, I'm so sorry.
对不起
I'm so sorry.
这些床单一股尿味
These sheets smell like piss.
对我们用的剂量的最终决定呢  女士们
Final verdict on the micro dosing, ladies?
绝对得用曼陀罗
Well, the Datura was definitely the right species.
真是调皮的小东西
It's a nasty little fucker.
但是我们能再多加点
But we coulda used more.
都怪我  我的炼金术还需要练习
That's on me. Yeah, I'm just growing into my alchemy.
这个平衡很微妙  因为我们希望他瘸
It's a delicate balance, 'cause you want him to go limp
出现幻觉  但不能死
and see shit but not die, right?
我只是想说
Well, I just wanna say
谢谢是肯定的
thank you, obviously.
卡拉刚给我打电话时  我承认我有所怀疑
When Kara first called me, I admit I was skeptical.
但是听起来你们真的改变了他
But it sounds like you really reached him.
或者他只是怕了  以为我们给他的屌下了巫毒术
Or he's just scared and thinks we put voodoo on his dick.
也许吧
Maybe.
但也许不是
But maybe not.
对我来说有区别
Well, it makes a difference to me.
他是我全部的家人了
He's my whole family.
你们不像我这么了解他
You don't know him like I do.
我们齐集一堂都有各自的理由  对吗
Well, we all have reasons for being here, right?
我的婚礼还有三小时就开始了  彼得
My wedding is in three hours, Peter.
你怎么有脸来
How can you possibly justify coming here?
就一分钟
For one minute.
我想见见我们的女儿  拜托你
I need to see our daughter, please.
一分钟
One minute,
就行了
and that's it.
-就行了  -天啊  你看上去一团糟
- Okay. - Jesus, you look like shit.
爸爸  你干什么
Dad, what are you doing?
-你没事吧  -没事...
- You okay? - Yeah, um...
我们能去散散步吗
could we go for a walk?
-嗯  -谢谢你
- Yeah. - Thank you.
敬放干了沼泽
To draining the swamp,
一次一个坏男人
one bad hombre at a time.
我觉得我们都可以好好干一杯
I think we can all drink to that.
这些小泡泡
Little stingy on the bubbly,
我能连喝三杯
I'm gonna need three of these.
太棒了
Amazing!
我一直将你的可贵之处当做理所当然的馈赠
I've taken for granted how precious you are and...
你每次也都原谅了我
and you let me get away with it every time,
但我不希望你再那样做了
but I don't want you to do that anymore.
不能为我  也不能为任何人这样
Not for me, not for any man.
我们再也不说谎了  宝贝
No more lies, baby, okay?
我不会再错过任何事
And I'm never gonna miss a thing.
我会参加你的每一场足球比赛
And I'll be at every soccer game from here on out,
我会跟其他父母一样背着
and I'm gonna be carrying one of those big plastic bags
装满橘子片的塑料袋  好吗
of orange slices like those other parents do, okay?
天啊  爸爸
Oh my God, Dad.
你要死了吗
Are you dying?
不不不  宝贝
No, no, no, baby.
我觉得我也许该死
I think maybe I should have.
但我还在这里
But I'm still here,
所以我是全世界
which makes me the luckiest man
最幸运的人
on the planet.
莱利  我爱你
Riley, I love you...
好爱你
so much.
明天见
I will see you tomorrow.
不是下个周末  就明天  好吗
Not next weekend, tomorrow, okay?
怎么回事
What is this?
你要死了还是怎么着吗
What, are you dying or something?
劳拉  我很抱歉  我在各个方面
Laura, I'm so sorry I failed you
都辜负了你
on every conceivable level.
不仅仅是我
It wasn't just me.
彼得
Hey, Peter.
你好
Hi-- hi, hello.
我们认识吗
Uh... do we know each other?
现在认识了
We do now.
乖乖的哦
Be good.
树屋